Darin M. Wallace

Technology Services

About

Senior Systems Developer II with 20+ years of experience supporting technology processes and quality services assurance. Expert in testing processes for a wide variety of applications and software, creating regression scripts in Gherkin language. Has knowledge and can develop in html, js, jquery, mysql, sql and mongo dbs. Possesses a Bachelor's Degree in Business Management.

Education

B.S. Business Management Washburn University, 1991 Topeka, Kansas

People Leader Training, 2013-2019

Scrum Master – A Servant Leader, 2019

International Institute for Software Testing, 2004-2010

Red Cross CPR/First Aid Instructor Certification, 2014

KU Bootcamp – FullStack Development, 2020

Skills

Microsoft Office Suite

Agile Team Processes

Organizational Communication

Collaborative Processes

Data Analysis

Development Languages:

Html

JavaScript

JQuery

MySql

Contact

6

(785-230-0862

 $\succ\!\!<$

darwall8@gmail.com



1278 SW High Ave. Topeka, Kansas 66604

in

Volunteering

Meals on Wheels, 2006-2019

Blood Bank Donations, every 2 months, 2000-2020

Corporate BNSF CPR/First Aid Instruction, 2014-2018

United Way

BNS Campaign Committee

Day of Caring

Citizen Panel, 2008-2012

TPS District Citizens Advisory Council, 2006-2010

Professional Experience

Topeka Public Schools 2020-current **College and Career Advocate, 2020-current** – Organized ACT bootcamp to prepare students for Act Test. Create monthly College and Career Newsletter, maintain scholarship database, organize and implement a Virtual College and Career Fair with over 60 presenters. Assists students with resume creation, college applications, scholarship application, and standardized test preparation.

BNSF Railway 1996-2020 Senior Systems Developer II , 2013-2020 – Work with a team in designing new platforms to modernize legacy applications for internal corporate clients. Assist with gathering of requirements to assist the design of the project. Test stories that developers have completed, creating defect documentation and demonstrating new applications to the client upon completion of the project.

Senior Systems Analyst, 2000-2013 TYE Compensation Specialist, 1996-2000

Kansas Department of Labor 1993-1996

Unemployment Claims Processor, 1993-2000 – Interviewed claimants applying for unemployment benefits and validated job search records of existing claimants.